Atri Banerjee

Application Developer in Microsoft Technology

Kolkata, West Bengal, India Mobile: +91 – 9674353071 Email: atri.tih@gmail.com Skype: atri.banerjee2011

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/atribanerjee

COVER LETTER

I am a self-employed developer. I work as a freelancer. I have more than 10 years' experience in application development in the IT industry. I have completed my Post Graduation degree in Computer Science and I also have Asp. Net certification from Hewlett Packard (HP). I can speak, read & write English fluently.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Asp.Net Core, Asp.Net 3.5/4.0/4.5/5.2, Asp.Net MVC 3/4/5, Razor, Web Api, JavaScript, JQuery, Windows Form Application, Windows Services, Web Services, Silverlight, Sql Server 2005/2008/2012/2014/2016/2019, MySql, C#, VB.Net, css3, bootstrap, KenoUI, Telerik, SignaR, Ajax, Html5, AngularJS, Visual Studio 2010/2012/2013/2015/2017 etc.

I am familiar with cloud services such as Azure & AWS as well. I have worked with App Services, Virtual Machines, Sql Databases, Storage Account (Blob, File) also worked with AWS as well. I have used the following AWS services such as Beanstalk, RDS, S3 Storage etc.

I can work with few SVN. Such as Visual Studio Online, TFS, GIT, Bitbucket etc. I am also familiar with few Payment Gateways, such as PayPal, PaySimple, Authorised Dot Net etc

I am also familiar with sending Email & SMS as well by using several apis, such as Sendgrid, Mailchimp, Amazon SES, Twilio, Jasper Api etc

REFERENCES

1. Bruce Matichuk

CTO, Co-Founder at Salu | Health Gauge Edmonton, Canada +17809643709

2. Chu Yves

276 Garibaldi Street, 69003, Lyon, La France +33-650362921

3. Robert Whitman

817 trophy way, bear, Delaware, 19702 +1 267-237-7416

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Application Developer

January 2016 - Present

Application Developer

Dreamztech Solutions Pvt Ltd - AQ 7 Ambient Building, 6th Floor, Salt Lake City, Sector - 5, Kolkata, West

Bengal, India

https://www.dreamztech.com

October 2012 - January 2016

Software Developer

ILICO Services Ltd - F2A, Latika Apartment - 3, Taruliya, Newtown, Kolkata, West Bengal, India

http://www.ilico.in

April 2012 - October 2012

Junior Web Developer

Jnanalok Technologies – 24 Bagha Jatin Road, Barahnagar, Kolkata, India

February 2011 - April 2012

EDUCATION

ASP. NET Certification

Hewlett Packard Inc, DLF IT Park, Kolkata, India February 2011 – May 2011

Masters in Computer Application

West Bengal University of Technology Techno India Hooghly 2008 – 2011

Bachelor of Science

University of Calcutta Bhairab Ganguly College 2003 – 2007